<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="Joke">
        <item>I couldn\'t fix your brakes, so I made your horn louder!</item>
        <item>Money talks ... but all mine ever says is goodbye!</item>
        <item>I\'m in shape ... round\'s a shape isn\'t it?</item>
        <item>I\'m not paranoid! Which of my enemies told you this?</item>
        <item>Hard work never hurt anyone, but why take the chance.</item>
        <item>I still miss my ex. But my aim is getting better.</item>
        <item>When I\'m not in my right mind, my left mind gets pretty crowded.</item>
        <item>Everything is funny as long as it is happening to somebody else.</item>
        <item>Doing nothing is very hard to do...you never know when you\'re finished.</item>
        <item>I only go to work on days that don\'t end in a \'y\'.</item>
        <item>If Harry Potter\'s so magical, why can\'t he cure his own eyesight?</item>
        <item>If the minimum wasn\'t acceptable it wouldn\'t be called the minimum.</item>
        <item>Beer – the reason I wake up every afternoon.</item>
        <item>Raising a kid is part joy and part guerrilla warfare.</item>
        <item>The following statement is true.\nThe previous statement is false.</item>
        <item>Light travels faster than sound. This is why some people appear bright until you hear them speak.</item>
        <item>My mother never saw the irony in calling me a son-of-a-bitch.</item>
        <item>Women might be able to fake orgasms. But men can fake a whole relationship.</item>
        <item>We never really grow up, we only learn how to act in public.</item>
        <item>Men have two emotions: Hungry and Horny. If you see him without an erection, make him a sandwich.</item>
        <item>I thought I wanted a career, turns out I just wanted paychecks.</item>
        <item>If 4 out of 5 people SUFFER from diarrhea… does that mean that one enjoys it?</item>
        <item>A bus station is where a bus stops. A train station is where a train stops. On my desk, I have a work station..</item>
        <item>If I agreed with you we\'d both be wrong.</item>
        <item>Did you know that dolphins are so smart that within a few weeks of captivity, they can train people to stand on the very edge of the pool and throw them fish?</item>
        <item>A computer once beat me at chess, but it was no match for me at kick boxing.</item>
        <item>If you think nobody cares if you’re alive, try missing a couple of payments.</item>
        <item>Sex is not the answer. Sex is the question. “Yes” is the answer.</item>
        <item>Evening news is where they begin with \'Good evening\', and then proceed to tell you why it isn\'t.</item>
        <item>Knowledge is knowing a tomato is a fruit; Wisdom is not putting it in a fruit salad.</item>
        <item>Never, under any circumstances, take a sleeping pill and a laxative on the same night.</item>
        <item>When I am sad, I sing, and then the world is sad with me.</item>
        <item>I\'m an atheist, thank God.</item>
        <item>Don\'t knock on death\'s door, ring the doorbell and run- he hates that.</item>
        <item>Reality is a hallucination brought on by lack of alcohol.</item>
        <item>People in cars cause accidents. Accidents in cars cause people.</item>
        <item>After all is said and done, more is said than done.</item>
        <item>Better late than really late.</item>
        <item>A good friend would come bail you out of jail. A great friend would be sitting in the jail cell with you saying, \'That was fun!\'.</item>
        <item>I asked God for a bike, but I know God doesn’t work that way. So I stole a bike and asked for forgiveness.</item>
        <item>I want to die peacefully in my sleep, like my grandfather.. Not screaming and yelling like the passengers in his car.</item>
        <item>Do not argue with an idiot. He will drag you down to his level and beat you with experience.</item>
        <item>The last thing I want to do is hurt you. But it\'s still on the list.</item>
        <item>If sex is a pain in the ass, then you\'re doing it wrong…</item>
        <item>Warning: Dates in calendar are closer than they appear.</item>
        <item>We live in a society where pizza gets to your house before the police.</item>
        <item>I saw a woman wearing a sweat shirt with \'Guess\' on it…so I said \'Implants?\'</item>
        <item>I didn\'t say it was your fault, I said I was blaming you.</item>
        <item>Whenever I fill out an application, in the part that says If an emergency, notify: I put DOCTOR. What\'s my mother going to do?</item>
        <item>To steal ideas from one person is plagiarism. To steal from many is research.</item>
        <item>Why does someone believe you when you say there are four billion stars, but check when you say the paint is wet?</item>
        <item>Better to remain silent and be thought a fool, than to speak and remove all doubt.</item>
        <item>A clear conscience is usually the sign of a bad memory.</item>
        <item>Good girls are bad girls that never get caught.</item>
        <item>He who smiles in a crisis has found someone to blame.</item>
        <item>Having sex is like playing bridge. If you don\'t have a good partner, you\'d better have a good hand.</item>
        <item>I love deadlines. I especially love the whooshing sound they make as they fly by.</item>
        <item>Good judgment comes from bad experience, and a lot of that comes from bad judgment.</item>
        <item>I think animal testing is a terrible idea; they get all nervous and give the wrong answers.</item>
        <item>There are three sides of an arguement -- your side, my side and the right side.</item>
        <item>There are three sides of an arguement -- your side, my side and the right side.</item>
        <item>The road to success is always under construction</item>
        <item>You know the speed of light..\nSo what is the speed of dark ?</item>
        <item>Always remember you\'re unique, just like everyone else.</item>
        <item>If at first you don\'t succeed; call it version 1.0</item>
        <item>I would love to change the world, but they won\'t give me the source code</item>
        <item>I saw six men kicking and punching the mother-in-law. My neighbor said \'Are you going to help?\'\n I said, \'No, Six should be enough.</item>
        <item>Everybody lies, but it doesn\'t matter since nobody listens.</item>
        <item>To be sure of hitting the target, shoot first. And, whatever you hit, call it the target.</item>
        <item>You have to stay in shape. My grandmother, she started walking five miles a day when she was 60. She\'s 97 today and we don\'t know where the hell she is.</item>
        <item>The quickest way to double your money is to fold it in half and put it back in your pocket.</item>
        <item>Arguing about whether the glass is half full or half empty misses the point, which is this: the bartender cheated you.</item>
        <item>Always forgive your enemies - Nothing annoys them so much.</item>
        <item>When everything\'s coming your way, you\'re in the wrong lane.</item>
        <item>For Sale: Parachute. Only used once, never opened, small stain.</item>
        <item>Do you have trouble making up your mind? Well, yes or no?</item>
        <item>If everything seems to be going well, you have obviously overlooked something.</item>
        <item>Everyone has a photographic memory. Some just don\'t have film.</item>
        <item>Join The Army, Visit exotic places, meet strange people, then kill them.</item>
        <item>Before borrowing money from a friend, decide which you need more.(Friend or Money!)</item>
        <item>Death is hereditary.</item>
        <item>An consultant is someone who takes a subject you understand and makes it sound confusing.</item>
        <item>Never argue with a fool. People might not know the difference.</item>
        <item>When you\'re right, no one remembers. When you\'re wrong, no one forgets.</item>
        <item>Cheer up, the worst is yet to come.</item>
        <item>Everyone makes mistakes. The trick is to make mistakes when nobody is looking.</item>
        <item>Always borrow money from a pessimist.He won\'t expect it back.</item>
        <item>I like work.It fascinates me.I sit and look at it for hours.</item>
        <item>Where there\'s a will, there are five hundred relatives.</item>
        <item>Everybody wants to go to heaven, but nobody wants to die.</item>
        <item>Last night I lay in bed looking up at the stars in the sky and I thought to myself, where the heck is the ceiling.</item>
        <item>A successful man is one who makes more money than his wife can spend. A successful woman is one who can find such a man.</item>
        <item>Use products that match your skin type—hydrating formulas for dry skin, water-based for oily skin and hypoallergenic for sensitive skin.\n-Lana Turner</item>
        <item>Marriage is give and take. You\'d better give it to her or she\'ll take it anyway. \n- Joey Adams</item>
        <item>I am not a vegetarian because I love animals; I am a vegetarian because I hate plants.\n-Whitney Brown</item>
        <item>All right everyone, line up alphabetically according to your height.\n-Casey Stengel</item>
        <item>Anyone who says he can see through women is missing a lot.\n-Groucho Marx</item>
        <item>Behind every great man is a woman rolling her eyes.\n-Jim Carrey</item>
        <item>Guys: No Shirt, No Service - Gals: No Shirt, No Charge</item>
        <item>Experience is what you have after you\'ve forgotten her name.\n-Milton Berle</item>
        <item>Man invented language to satisfy his deep need to complain.\n-Lily Tomlin</item>
        <item>I am not afraid of death, I just don\'t want to be there when it happens.\n-Woody Allen</item>
        <item>I don\'t think anyone should write their autobiography until after they\'re dead.\n-Samuel Goldwyn</item>
        <item>I drank some boiling water because I wanted to whistle.\n-Mitch Hedberg</item>
        <item>I found there was only one way to look thin: hang out with fat people.\n-Rodney Dangerfield</item>
        <item>I have a love interest in every one of my films: A gun.\n-Arnold Schwarzenegger</item>
        <item>I never drink water because of the disgusting things that fish do in it.\n-W. C. Fields</item>
        <item>I used to sell furniture for a living. The trouble was, it was my own.\n-Les Dawson</item>
        <item>In comic strips, the person on the left always speaks first.\n-George Carlin</item>
        <item>It is easy for me to love myself, but for ladies to do it is another question altogether.\n-Johnny Vegas</item>
        <item>My fake plants died because I did not pretend to water them.\n-Mitch Hedberg</item>
        <item>People always ask me, \'Were you funny as a child?\' Well, no, I was an accountant.\n-Ellen DeGeneres</item>
        <item>Recession is when a neighbor loses his job. Depression is when you lose yours.\n-Ronald Reagan</item>
        <item>There are only three things women need in life: food, water, and compliments.\n-Chris Rock</item>
        <item>Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I\'m not sure about the universe.\n-Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>Weather forecast for tonight: Dark.\n-George Carlin</item>
        <item>When I go to a bar, I don\'t go looking for a girl who knows the capital of Maine.\n-David Brenner</item>
        <item>Politicians and diapers have one thing in common. They should both be changed regularly, and for the same reason.</item>
        <item>A graduation ceremony is an event where the commencement speaker tells thousands of students dressed in identical caps and gowns that \'individuality\' is the key to success.</item>
        <item>Why do Americans choose from just two people to run for president and 50 for Miss America?</item>
        <item>Some cause happiness wherever they go; others whenever they go</item>
        <item>We have enough gun control. What we need is idiot control.</item>
        <item>No doubt exists that all women are crazy; it\'s only a question of degree.\n- W. C. Fields</item>
        <item>Some people hear voices.. Some see invisible people.. Others have no imagination whatsoever.</item>
        <item>I thought I wanted a career, turns out I just wanted paychecks.</item>
        <item>A diplomat is someone who can tell you to go to hell in such a way that you will look forward to the trip.</item>
        <item>I don\'t suffer from insanity; I enjoy every minute of it.</item>
        <item>Why is the place you drive on is a parkway, and the place you park on is the driveway?</item>
        <item>Golf is a game whose aim is to hit a very small ball into an even smaller hole, with weapons singularly ill-designed for the purpose.\n- Winston Churchill</item>
        <item>There\'s a fine line between cuddling and holding someone down so they can\'t get away.</item>
        <item>A professor is one who talks in someone else\'s sleep\n- H. Auden</item>
        <item>Don\'t wait for a light to appear at the end of the tunnel, stride down there and light the bloody thing yourself.</item>
        <item>Patience is something you admire in the driver behind you, but not in one ahead.</item>
        <item>The hardest thing in the world to understand is the income tax.\n- Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>A bus is a vehicle that runs twice as fast when you are after it as when you are in it.</item>
        <item>Washington is a place where politicians don\'t know which way is up and taxes don\'t know which way is down.\n- Robert Orben</item>
        <item>I don\'t know what weapons will be used in world war three, but in world war four people will use sticks and stones.\n- Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>Just remember...if the world didn\'t suck, we\'d all fall off.</item>
        <item>What do you call a black man flying a plane? A pilot you racist.</item>
        <item>I\'m gonna put a curse on you and all your kids will be born completely naked.\n- Jimi Hendrix</item>
        <item>Love is like a booger. You keep picking at it until you get it, then wonder what to do with it.</item>
        <item>Why don\'t they make the whole plane out of that black box stuff.</item>
        <item>I had a dream last night, I was eating a ten pound marshmallow. I woke up this morning and the pillow was gone.</item>
        <item>You spend the first 2 years of their life teaching them to walk and talk. Then you spend the next 16 telling them to sit down and shut-up.</item>
        <item>Maybe in order to understand mankind we have to look at that word itself. MANKIND. Basically, it\'s made up of two separate words mank and ind. What do these words mean? It\'s a mystery and that\'s why so is mankind.\n- Jack Handy</item>
        <item>Artificial intelligence is no match for natural stupidity.</item>
        <item>God gave men both a penis and a brain, but unfortunately not enough blood supply to run both at the same time.\n- Robin Williams</item>
        <item>Without question, the greatest invention in the history of mankind is beer. Oh, I grant you that the wheel was also a fine invention, but the wheel does not go nearly as well with pizza.\n- Dave Barry</item>
        <item>It\'s strange, isn\'t it. You stand in the middle of a library and go aaaaagghhhh and everyone just stares at you. But you do the same thing on an aeroplane, and everyone joins in.\n- Tommy Cooper</item>
        <item>Never get into fights with ugly people, they have nothing to lose.</item>
        <item>It\'s not the fall that kills you; it\'s the sudden stop at the end.</item>
        <item>If at first you don\'t succeed, skydiving is not for you!</item>
        <item>If the world were ruled by women then there would be no war… just couple of nations not talking with each other.</item>
        <item>Women sleep on the right side of the bed because even while sleeping they have to be right!</item>
        <item>I have great faith in fools; self-confidence my friends call it.</item>
        <item>It’s not cheating unless you get caught.</item>
        <item>Quitting smoking is the easiest thing in the world. I\'ve done it dozens of times.</item>
        <item>I hope life isn\'t a joke, because I don\'t get it.</item>
        <item>Avoid hangovers: stay drunk.</item>
        <item>Most people are only alive because it is illegal to shoot them.</item>
        <item>Girls want a lot of things from one guy. Conversely, guys want one thing from a lot of girls.</item>
        <item>I\'ve got problem for your solution…</item>
        <item>When I was born I was so surprised I didn\'t talk for a year and a half.</item>
        <item>Do you believe in love at first sight or should I walk by again ?</item>
        <item>Practice makes perfect but then nobody is perfect so wats the point of practicing?</item>
        <item>Some people are like Slinky\'s. Pretty much useless but make you smile when you push them down the stairs.</item>
        <item>You cry, I cry, ….you laugh, I laugh…you jump off a cliff i laugh even harder!!</item>
        <item>Never judge someone until you walk a mile in their shoes. By that time, they\'ll be a mile away and barefoot.</item>
        <item>Never steal.\nThe government hates competition.</item>
        <item>I want to kill the hottest person alive… but suicide is a crime!</item>
        <item>DON\'T HIT KIDS!!!\nNo, seriously, they have guns now.</item>
        <item>Rule #1 I\'m always right\nRule #2 If i\'m wrong please look at rule #1</item>
        <item>Regular naps prevent old age, especially if you take them while driving.</item>
        <item>Having one child makes you a parent; having two you are a referee.</item>
        <item>Marriage is a relationship in which one person is always right and the other is the husband!</item>
        <item>I believe we should all pay our tax with a smile. I tried - but they wanted cash.</item>
        <item>Don\'t feel bad. A lot of people have no talent.</item>
        <item>Don\'t marry the person you want to live with, marry the one you cannot live without, but whatever you do, you\'ll regret it later.</item>
        <item>You can\'t buy love, but you pay heavily for it.</item>
        <item>Bad officials are elected by good citizens who do not vote.</item>
        <item>Laziness is nothing more than the habit of resting before you get tired.</item>
        <item>Marriage is give and take. You\'d better give it to her or she will take it anyway.</item>
        <item>My wife and I always compromise. I admit I\'m wrong and she agrees with me.</item>
        <item>Those who can\'t laugh at themselves leave the job to others.</item>
        <item>Ladies first. Pretty ladies sooner.</item>
        <item>A successful marriage requires falling in love many times, always with the same person.</item>
        <item>You are getting old when you enjoy remembering things more than doing them.</item>
        <item>It doesn\'t matter how often a married man changes his job, he still ends up with the same boss.</item>
        <item>Saving is the best thing. Especially when your parents have done it for you.</item>
        <item>It\'s funny when people discuss Love Marriage vs Arranged. It\'s like asking someone, if suicide is better or being murdered.</item>
        <item>There is only one perfect child in the world and every mother has it.</item>
        <item>It is no exaggeration to say that the undecided could go one way or another.</item>
        <item>He who laughs last probably does not get the joke.</item>
        <item>If you smacked a kid in the face with a bottle of Johnson\'s No More Tears, would it create beautiful irony?</item>
        <item>Depression is just anger without enthusiasm.</item>
        <item>Yo momma\'s so fat, she walked past the TV and i missed the first season of Lost.</item>
        <item>The most effective copyright protection known to man : a scratched CD.</item>
        <item>It appears the location of my fist and your head are not mutually exclusive! It is a probability miracle!</item>
        <item>Coffee just isn\'t my cup of tea.</item>
        <item>I just broke up with someone and the last thing she said to me was You\'ll never find anyone like me again! I\'m thinking, I should hope not! If I don\'t want you, why would I want someone like you.</item>
        <item>I am so clever that sometimes I don\'t understand a single word of what I am saying.</item>
        <item>Love is like a booger. You keep picking at it until you get it, then wonder what to do with it.</item>
        <item>You know, somebody actually complimented me on my driving today. They left a little note on the windscreen, it said \'Parking Fine.\'</item>
        <item>An archaeologist is the best husband a woman can have. The older she gets the more interested he is in her.</item>
        <item>Many people quit looking for work when they find a job.</item>
        <item>I read somewhere that 77 per cent of all the mentally ill live in poverty. Actually, I\'m more intrigued by the 23 percent who are apparently doing quite well for themselves.</item>
        <item>Ah, yes, divorce..., from the Latin word meaning to rip out a man\'s genitals through his wallet.</item>
        <item>Women need a reason to have sex. Men just need a place.</item>
        <item>And God said: \'Let there be Satan, so people don\'t blame everything on me. And let there be lawyers,so people don\'t blame everything on Satan.</item>
        <item>Written very small on the back poket of a girl\'s jeans - \'If you can read this, you\'re WAY too close.\'</item>
        <item>Don\'t believe that sort of rubbish, unless you hear it from me.</item>
        <item>Whoever coined the phrase Quiet as a mouse has never stepped on one.</item>
        <item>UNIX is basically a simple operating system, but you have to be a genius to understand the simplicity.</item>
        <item>Never believe anything in politics until it has been officially denied.</item>
        <item>A celebrity is a person who works hard all his life to become well known, then wears dark glasses to avoid being recognized.</item>
        <item>A compromise is an agreement whereby both parties get what neither of them wanted.</item>
        <item>A conclusion is the place where you got tired of thinking.</item>
        <item>All my life, I always wanted to be somebody. Now I see that I should have been more specific.</item>
        <item>Anybody can win, unless there happens to be a second entry.</item>
        <item>An expert is a man who tells you a simple thing in a confused way in such a fashion as to make you think the confusion is your own fault.</item>
        <item>Maybe this world is another planet\'s hell.</item>
        <item>The chicken came first - God would look silly sitting on an egg.</item>
        <item>Can we actually know the universe? My God, it\'s hard enough finding your way around in Chinatown.</item>
        <item>Who says nothing is impossible. I\'ve been doing nothing for years.</item>
        <item>I used to eat a lot of natural foods until I learned that most people die of natural causes.</item>
        <item>The first thing men notice about a woman is her eyes. Then, when her eyes aren\'t looking, they notice her breasts.</item>
        <item>An open marriage is nature\'s way of telling you that you need a divorce.</item>
        <item>I\'ve never been to an Al-Qaeda Christmas party, but I have seen the invites. No music, no dancing, but we promise the fastest game of pass the parcel you\'ve ever seen.</item>
        <item>Age to women is like Kryptonite to Superman.</item>
        <item>I\'m so old they\'ve cancelled my blood type.</item>
        <item>You know you\'re getting fat when you can pinch an inch on your forehead.</item>
        <item>As you get older, the pickings get slimmer, but the people don\'t.</item>
        <item>People say that age is just a state of mind. I say it\'s more about the state of your body.</item>
        <item>One should never trust a woman who tells her real age. If she tells that, she\'ll tell anything.</item>
        <item>By the time you\'re eighty years old you\'ve learned everything. You only have to remember it.</item>
        <item>When you become senile, you won\'t know it.</item>
        <item>Inflation is when you pay fifteen dollars for the ten-dollar haircut you used to get for five dollars when you had hair.</item>
        <item>First you forget names, then you forget faces, then you forget to pull your zipper up, then you forget to pull your zipper down.</item>
        <item>Women have a passion for mathematics. They divide their age in half, double the price of their clothes, and always add at least five years to the age of their best friend.</item>
        <item>A liberated woman is one who has sex before marriage and a job after.</item>
        <item>You don\'t know a women till you\'ve met her in court.</item>
        <item>I wonder why it is, that young men are always cautioned against bad girls. Anyone can handle a bad girl. It\'s the good girls men should be warned against.</item>
        <item>One of the most difficult things in the world is to convince a woman that even a bargain costs money.</item>
        <item>I chased a girl for two years only to discover that her tastes were exactly like mine: We were both crazy about girls.</item>
        <item>A woman\'s mind is cleaner than a man\'s. She changes it more often.</item>
        <item>Instead of getting married again, I\'m going to find a woman I don\'t like and just give her a house.</item>
        <item>My wife is a sex object - every time I ask for sex, she objects.</item>
        <item>A psychiatrist is a fellow who asks you a lot of expensive questions your wife asks for nothing.</item>
        <item>A woman knows she\'s wearing the right dress, when her man wants to take it off.</item>
        <item>A good politician is quite as unthinkable as an honest burglar.</item>
        <item>Politics is perhaps the only profession for which no preparation is thought necessary.</item>
        <item>A politician is a fellow who will lay down your life for his country.</item>
        <item>The mistake a lot of politicians make is in forgetting they\'ve been appointed and thinking they\'ve been anointed.</item>
        <item>The word \'politics\' is derived from the word \'poly\', meaning \'many\', and the word \'ticks\', meaning \'blood sucking parasites\'.</item>
        <item>Everything is changing. People are taking the comedians seriously and the politicians as a joke.</item>
        <item>The difference between fiction and reality? Fiction has to make sense.</item>
        <item>Until I was 13, I thought my name was \'Shut Up.\'</item>
        <item>Human beings are the only creatures on earth that allow their children to come back home.</item>
        <item>And my parents finally realise that I\'m kidnapped and they snap into action immediately: they rent out my room.</item>
        <item>When I was born ... the doctor came out to the waiting room and said to my father ... I\'m very sorry. We did everything we could ... but he pulled through.</item>
        <item>It\'s a scientific fact. For every year a person lives in Hollywood, they lose two points of their IQ.</item>
        <item>I thought \'Deep Throat\' was a movie about a giraffe.</item>
        <item>Half the people in Hollywood are dying to be discovered and the other half are afraid they will be.</item>
        <item>The only \'ism\' Hollywood believes in is plagiarism.</item>
        <item>Talk low, talk slow, and don\'t say too much.</item>
        <item>People tell me that Senator Edwards got picked for his good looks, his sex appeal, and his great hair. I say to them, \'How do you think I got the job?</item>
        <item>I refuse to answer that question on the grounds that I don\'t know the answer.</item>
        <item>I am free of all prejudices. I hate everyone equally.</item>
        <item>I can resist everything except temptation.</item>
        <item>I once spent a year in Philadelphia, I think it was on a Sunday.</item>
        <item>Remember, today is the tomorrow you worried about yesterday.</item>
        <item>I don\'t make jokes. I just watch the government and report the facts.\n- Will Rogers</item>
        <item>If you can\'t convince them, confuse them.\n- Harry S. Truman</item>
        <item>We\'ve all met people who are supposedly incredibly intelligent but don\'t know which way to sit on a lavatory.\n- Stephen Fry</item>
        <item>I have six locks on my door all in a row. When I go out, I only lock every other one. I figure no matter how long somebody stands there picking the locks, they are always locking three.\n- Elayne Boosler</item>
        <item>An intellectual is someone who has found something more interesting than sex.\n- Edgar Wallace</item>
        <item>Great minds discuss ideas. Average minds discuss events. Small minds discuss people.</item>
        <item>Skill is successfully walking a tightrope over Niagara Falls. Intelligence is not trying.</item>
        <item>I think the worst time to have a heart attack is during a game of charades...or a game of fake heart attack.\n- Demetri Martin</item>
        <item>My wife was fitted with a coil. For about 18 months I hated it! She used to pick up CB signals.\n- Bob Monkhouse</item>
        <item>I used to have Mad Cow\'s disease, but I\'m alright Nooooooooow.\n- Billy Connolly</item>
        <item>I know why Superman left Krypton. Earth was the only place he could get steroids!\n- Milton Berle</item>
        <item>I went to a meeting for premature ejaculators. I left early.\n- Jack Benny</item>
        <item>I met this guy who said he loved children, then I found out he was on parole for it.\n- Monica Piper</item>
        <item>I had lunch with a chess champion the other day. I knew he was a chess champion because it took him 20 minutes to pass the salt.\n- Eric Sykes</item>
        <item>Duct tape is like the Force. It has a light side, a dark side, and it holds the universe together.\n- Carl Zwanzig</item>
        <item>When I was a kid my favorite relative was Uncle Caveman. After school we\'d all go play in his cave, and every once in a while he would eat one of us. It wasn\'t until later that I found out that Uncle Caveman was a bear.\n- Jack Handey</item>
        <item>I told my wife the truth. I told her I was seeing a psychiatrist. Then she told me the truth: that she was seeing a psychiatrist, two plumbers, and a bartender.\n- Rodney Dangerfield</item>
        <item>I had plenty of pimples as a kid. One day I fell asleep in the library. When I woke up, a blind man was reading my face.\n- Rodney Dangerfield</item>
        <item>So I said, \'Where do you want to go for your anniversary?\'\nShe said: \'I want to go somewhere I\'ve never been before.\'\nI said, \'Try the kitchen.\'\n- Henry Youngman</item>
        <item>I said to the wife : Guess what I heard in the pub? They reckon the milkman has made love to every woman in this road except one. And she said : I\'ll bet it\'s that stuck up Phyllis at number 23.\n- Max Kauffmann</item>
        <item>I sold my house this week. I got a pretty good price for it, but it made my landlord mad as hell.\n- Garry Shandling</item>
        <item>I\'ve often wanted to drown my troubles, but I can\'t get my wife to go swimming.\n- Jimmy Carter</item>
        <item>The toilets at a local police station have been stolen. Police say they have nothing to go on.</item>
        <item>A woman tells her doctor, I\'ve got a bad back.\nThe doctor : It\'s old age.\nThe woman says:I want a second opinion.\nThe doctor says:Okay - you\'re ugly as well.\n- Tommy Cooper</item>
        <item>We used to play spin the bottle when I was a kid. A girl would spin the bottle and if it pointed to you when it stopped, the girl could either kiss you or give you a dime. By the time I was 14, I owned my own home.\n- Gene Perret</item>
        <item>So one day as a kid I was at the local Zoo. I was bored and kept pestering my Dad to go and play. Eventually he agreed, took me over to the lion enclosure, threw me in and said: There ya go, play dead...\n- Robert Paul</item>
        <item>I went to a bookstore and asked the saleswoman where the Self Help section was. She said if she told me it would defeat the purpose.\n- Dennis Miller</item>
        <item>Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that, who cares? ...He\'s a mile away and you\'ve got his shoes.\n- Billy Connolly</item>
        <item>My Dad used to say \'always fight fire with fire\', which is probably why he got thrown out of the the fire brigade.\n- Harry Hill</item>
        <item>I had plastic surgery last week. I cut up my credit cards.\n- Henry Youngman</item>
        <item>Foot: A special device for finding furniture in the dark.</item>
        <item>Police arrested two kids yesterday, one was drinking battery acid, the other was eating fireworks. They charged one and let the other one off.\n- Tommy Cooper</item>
        <item>My neighbour asked if he could use my lawnmower and I told him of course he could, so long as he didn\'t take it out of my garden.\n- Eric Morecambe</item>
        <item>You know, somebody actually complimented me on my driving today. They left a little note on the windscreen, it said \'Parking Fine.\' So that was nice.\n- Tommy Cooper</item>
        <item>Cos it\'s strange, isn\'t it. You stand in the middle of a library and go \'Aaaaaagghhh!!\' and everyone just stares at you. But you do the same thing on an aeroplane, and everyone joins in.\n- Tommy Cooper</item>
        <item>Employee of the month is a good example of how somebody can be both a winner and a loser at the same time.\n- Demetri Martin</item>
        <item>Doing nothing is very hard to do...you never know when you\'re finished.\n- Leslie Nielsen</item>
        <item>The trouble with unemployment is that the minute you wake up in the morning you\'re on the job.\n- Slappy White</item>
        <item>I like work: it fascinates me. I can sit and look at it for hours.</item>
        <item>The easiest job in the world has to be coroner. Surgery on dead people. What\'s the worst thing that could happen? If everything went wrong, maybe you\'d get a pulse\n- Dennis Miller</item>
        <item>I always arrive late at the office, but I make up for it by leaving early.\n- Charles Lamb</item>
        <item>The first sign of a nervous breakdown is when you start thinking your work is terribly important.\n- Milo Bloom</item>
        <item>If it weren\'t for the last minute, nothing would get done...</item>
        <item>The brain is a wonderful organ. It starts working when you get up in the morning, and doesn\'t stop until you get to the office.\n- Robert Frost</item>
        <item>The trouble with the rat race is that even if you win, you\'re still a rat.\n- Lily Tomlin</item>
        <item>The world is full of willing people; some willing to work, the rest willing to let them.\n- Robert Frost</item>
        <item>The golden rule of work is that the bosses jokes are ALWAYS funny.\n- Robert Paul</item>
        <item>When did I realize I was God? Well, I was praying and I suddenly realized I was talking to myself.\n- Peter OToole</item>
        <item>If you want to make God laugh, tell him your future plans.\n- Woody Allen</item>
        <item>In the first place God made idiots; that was for practice; then he made school boards.\n- Mark Twain</item>
        <item>Kids. They\'re not easy. But there has to be some penalty for sex.\n- Bill Maher</item>
        <item>There are only two things a child will share willingly :: communicable diseases and his mother\'s age.\n- Benjamin Spock</item>
        <item>Pretty much all the honest truth telling there is in the world is done by children.\n- Oliver Wendell Holmes</item>
        <item>A little girl at the wedding afterwards asked her mother why the bride changed her mind. What do you mean? responded her mother. Well, she went down the aisle with one man, and came back with another.</item>
        <item>Sex is nature, and I believe in going along with nature.\n- Marilyn Monroe</item>
        <item>It isn\'t premarital sex if you have no intention of getting married.\n- Drew Carey</item>
        <item>The last time I was inside a woman was when I was inside the Statue of Liberty.\n- Woody Allen</item>
        <item>Sex is more fun than cars but cars refuel quicker than men.\n- Germaine Greer</item>
        <item>Women need a reason to have sex, men just need a place.\n- Billy Crystal</item>
        <item>I blame my mother for my poor sex life. All she told me was, \'the man goes on top and the woman underneath\'. For three years my husband and I slept on bunk beds.\n- Joan Rivers</item>
        <item>If sex is such a natural phenomenon, how come there are so many books on how to?\n- Bette Midler</item>
        <item>As a lover, I\'m about as impressive as a magician on the radio.\n- Scott Roeben</item>
        <item>Sex is like art. Most of it is pretty bad, and the good stuff is out of your price range.\n- Scott Roeben</item>
        <item>Computers will never take the place of books. You can\'t stand on a floppy disk to reach a high shelf.\n- Sam Ewing</item>
        <item>They\'ve finally come up with the perfect office computer. If it makes a mistake, it blames another computer.\n- Milton Berle</item>
        <item>Always be wary of the Software Engineer who carries a screwdriver.\n- Robert Paul</item>
        <item>A computer once beat me at chess, but it was no match for me at kick boxing.\n- Emo Philips</item>
        <item>Men will confess to treason, murder, arson, false teeth, or a wig. How many of them will own up to a lack of humor?\n- Frank Moore Colby</item>
        <item>Humor is just another defense against the universe.\n- Mel Brooks</item>
        <item>What matters is not the length of the wand, but the magic in the stick.</item>
        <item>In view of the fact that God limited the intelligence of man, it seems unfair that he did not also limit his stupidity.\n- Konrad Adenauer</item>
        <item>Most fools think they are only ignorant.\n- Benjamin Franklin</item>
        <item>Only two things are infinite, the universe and human stupidity, and I\'m not sure about the former.\n- Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>When an actor marries an actress they both fight for the mirror.\n- Burt Reynolds</item>
        <item>Why get married and make one man miserable when I can stay single and make thousands miserable?\n- Carrie Snow</item>
        <item>The Three Ages of Marriage: Twenty is when you watch the TV after. Forty is when you watch the TV during. Sixty is when you watch the TV instead.</item>
        <item>Always get married early in the morning. That way, if it doesn\'t work out, you haven\'t wasted a whole day.\n- Mickey Rooney</item>
        <item>I think men who have a pierced ear are better prepared for marriage. They\'ve experienced pain and bought jewelry.\n- Rita Rudner</item>
        <item>Getting married is very much like going to a restaurant with friends. You order what you want, then when you see what the other fellow has, you wish you had ordered that.</item>
        <item>My wife and I were happy for twenty years. Then we met.\n- Rodney Dangerfield</item>
        <item>I\'ve had bad luck with both my wives. The first one left me and the second one didn\'t.\n- Patrick Murray</item>
        <item>Whatever you may look like, marry a man your own age - as your beauty fades, so will his eyesight.\n- Phyllis Diller</item>
        <item>I never knew what real happiness was until I got married. And by then it was too late.\n- Max Kauffmann</item>
        <item>Marriage changes passion ... suddenly you\'re in bed with a relative.</item>
        <item>Keep your eyes wide open before marriage, and half-shut afterwards.\n- Benjamin Franklin</item>
        <item>They say marriages are made in Heaven. But so is thunder and lightning.\n- Clint Eastwood</item>
        <item>Marriage is like pi - natural, irrational, and very important.\n- Lisa Hoffman</item>
        <item>A candidate is someone who gets money from the rich and votes from the poor to protect them from each other.</item>
        <item>Never pass up an opportunity to keep your mouth shut.\n- Paul Miller</item>
        <item>There are only two kinds of men - the dead and the deadly.\n- Helen Rowland</item>
        <item>If you never want to see a man again, say, \'I love you, I want to marry you. I want to have children...\' - they leave skid marks.\n- Rita Rudner</item>
        <item>To attract men, I wear a perfume called \'New Car Interior\'.\n- Rita Rudner</item>
        <item>Men can read maps better than women. Cause only the male mind could conceive of one inch equalling a hundred miles.\n- Roseanne Barr</item>
        <item>See, the problem is that God gives men a brain and a penis, and only enough blood to run one at a time.\n- Robin Williams</item>
        <item>If you die in an elevator, be sure to push the Up button.\n- Sam Levenson</item>
        <item>Death is life\'s way of telling you you\'re fired.</item>
        <item>I always advise people never to give advice.\n- P. G. Wodehouse</item>
        <item>Advice is what we ask for when we already know the answer but wish we didn\'t.\n- Erica Jong</item>
        <item>Never take a blind date to a silent film.\n- Geoffrey Parfitt</item>
        <item>Don\'t take life too seriously, you\'ll never get out of it alive.\n- Elbert Hubbard</item>
        <item>Always and never are two words you should always remember never to use.\n- Wendell Johnson</item>
        <item>I know I\'m getting better at golf because I\'m hitting fewer spectators.\n- Gerald R. Ford</item>
        <item>Some cause happiness wherever they go; others, whenever they go.\n- Oscar Wilde</item>
        <item>Happiness is like a kiss. You must share it to enjoy it.\n- Bernard Meltzer</item>
        <item>There is only one way to achieve happiness on this terrestrial ball, and that is to have either a clear conscience or none at all.\n- Ogden Nash</item>
        <item>NBC - No Body Cares.\n- Jay Leno</item>
        <item>I find television very educating. Every time somebody turns on the set, I go into the other room and read a book.\n- Groucho Marx</item>
        <item>You go to your TV to turn your brain off. You go to the computer when you want to turn your brain on.\n- Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>Television has raised writing to a new low. \n- Samuel Goldwyn</item>
        <item>If you rest, you rust.\n- Helen Hayes</item>
        <item>In three words I can sum up everything I\'ve learned about life: it goes on. \n- Robert Frost</item>
        <item>I recently read that love is entirely a matter of chemistry. That must be why my wife treats me like toxic waste. \n- David Bissonnette</item>
        <item>Actually, it only takes one drink to get me loaded. Trouble is, I can\'t remember if it\'s the thirteenth or fourteenth. \n- George Burns</item>
        <item>You\'re not drunk if you can lie on the floor without holding on. \n- Dean Martin</item>
        <item>If you want to know what God thinks of money, just look at the people he gave it to. \n- Dorothy Parker</item>
        <item>(Love) A temporary insanity curable by marriage. \n- Ambrose Bierce</item>
        <item>You can be young without money but you can\'t be old without it. \n- Tennessee Williams</item>
        <item>The safe way to double your money is to fold it over once and put it in your pocket. \n- Frank McKinney Hubbard</item>
        <item>When I read about the evils of drinking, I gave up reading. \n- Henry Youngman</item>
        <item>Coffee isn\'t my cup of tea. \n- Samuel Goldwyn</item>
        <item>He is accelerating all the time. That last lap was run in 64 seconds and the one before in 62. \n- David Coleman</item>
        <item>Have you noticed that all the people in favour of birth control are already born? \n- Benny Hill</item>
        <item>Common looking people are the best in the world: that is the reason the Lord makes so many of them. \n- Abraham Lincoln</item>
        <item>What do you call 500 lawyers lying on the bottom of the Ocean?\nA good start... \n- Danny DeVito</item>
        <item>I\'m trying to read a book on how to relax, but I keep falling asleep. \n- Jim Loy</item>
        <item>A good novel tells us the truth about it\'s hero; but a bad novel tells us the truth about its author. \n- G. K. Chesterton</item>
        <item>If you are first you are first. If you are second you are nothing. \n- Bill Shankly</item>
        <item>Football\'s not a matter of life and death ... it\'s more important than that. \n- Bill Shankly</item>
        <item>I used so much hairspray that I feel personally responsible for global warming. \n- Dusty Springfield</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>